So there's two options ahead of you.
Do you agree?
This is important.
So is Donald Trump,
okay let me ask a question back
because you're asking me questions.
You're not answering the basic point.
Do you think Donald Trump is dismantling the Constitution?
Can we agree that Donald Trump is dismantling it?
Because I'll agree with you on that.
I think he is dismantling the Constitution.
I think he's-
Illegally, unconstitutionally, undemocratic.
I think he's interpreting it in ways that are more-
Which judges do not agree with him on.
Okay, hold on.
Which the Supreme Court has not agreed with him on.
And the judges don't agree
with the people who wrote the Constitution.
How do you know that?
Okay, let's take your example of the Second Amendment.
Let's say that a bunch of judges-
I didn't give the Second Amendment.
No, no, no, hold on, hold on, hold on.
I said first, fourth,
you don't want to talk about the ones I've given.
No, you're interrupting me, you're interrupting me.
Let me say them one more time.
Because you're ignoring me.
First, fourth, fifth, 14th, 22nd Amendments.
Those are my amendments that I came with today.
I'm trying-
If you don't want to debate them, just say so.
I'm trying to understand your ideology.
You believe that dismantling the Constitution is okay-
You won't talk about the first, fourth, fifth-
When it's about parts of the Constitution
that you disagree with.
14th, 22nd Amendments.
You would be fine getting rid of the Second Amendment
even though that would be a dismantling of the Constitution.
No, because it would be done via Constitution.
It means I'm not the one sitting here like your pal-
Okay, you have agreed.
You have agreed the Constitution-
I'm not the one saying you just get rid of them willy-nilly.
I don't agree.
We're ramping up, we're ramping up.
I'm changing it.
I don't agree that Joe Biden should come in
and say by executive order,
if Joe Biden put out an executive order saying,
Second Amendment no longer applies,
I can round up everyone's guns.
I don't agree with that.
Your result is exactly the same.
I don't agree with them.
No, but I don't agree with the method of doing it.
It's unconstitutional.
That's fine.
And I would have said so,
but you can't bring yourself to say so.
We've been sitting here for several minutes.
All of your friends have seen me ask you several times.
Do you agree that Donald Trump is defying
the first, fourth, fifth, 14th,
and possibly 22nd Amendments?
Your colleague at least admitted
that he's defying the First Amendment.
I understand that you came in here.
What you are attempting to do
is simply frame this conversation
like you did with the first claim about Donald Trump.
But then when anybody asks you any kind of question
that presses you to the least degree about-
No, I answered.
I said I would dismantle the Constitution,
but I would do it constitutionally.
Okay.
Not by executive order.
What I'm trying to get to
is to prove to everybody who's watching
that what you care about is not the Constitution
in what it represents or creates.
You care about the Constitution
only insofar as it allows you
to achieve your political worldview.
We agree on that.
No, I care about the Constitution-
You agree with the Constitution.
Because I don't think presidents
should be fascist dictators and violate the Constitution.
That's what I'm saying.
You care-
And he is defying-
I don't think the president should have the power
to lock you and me up if we write an op-ed
that he doesn't like.
That's awesome.
I agree.
I don't think the president should be able
to crack down on us if you and I
decide to go protest-
I agree with you.
Outside his parade.
I don't think the president should be able
to deprive you and I of due process
or come into our homes-
I agree with you.
Without a worry.
And I think-
Well, let's end on agreement then.
All right, pause.
You've been voted out.
I'm glad we ended on agreement.
It's good to meet you.
It's good to meet you, Kai.
Good to meet you, Kai.